Okay so now we're going to start on the neck, going to oil in darks, a bit of oil,
to make this off, just going to oil that in.
Then if you come further down you can see where you've painted over and where you haven't.
Okay starting with the darkest dark first, that'll be in the neck,
the, I'll be in that, it's going to be in there. Okay I'm just going to,
I'm just loosely drawing in some of these creases, don't plan to get into this.
So creases, lighting this up so we can see what we're doing.
All right just on the edge, okay so a core shadow on the edge of the jaw,
going with some violet and burnt umber, I'll just get this darker along the
number, a bit of a gradation, so the shadow comes around the neck, a bit of reflected light
in here, okay then up around here, it's a bit lighter, it's going to be burnt umber,
touch of red, maybe orange, too light, red side, okay a bit darker on the neck there,
okay then looking at the hair on this side, quite dark in there, so go with the violet
burnt umber along the transition, that's going to be slightly darker,
this looks like a burnt umber, maybe yellow in there, okay, such more burnt umber,
it gets darker, okay then we can soften that edge, the violet burnt umber,
a bit darker on this edge here, then you can soften that, that burnt umber violet,
a number of the um the shadow, you can just call that burnt umber, call that a bit of mid-yellow,
edge, bit of violet, edge, up in that transition, look out that shape of the neck,
it's going to be the, as in green, yellow in there, okay, call that the neck done,
so that's not the neck done, it's going to pour some of these strands of hair out,
put something around the orange on the yellow side, a bit of these general shapes,
now calling it a bit lighter, so we've got some hair on this other side,
I think I'll just lubricate the background, I would go out and put that stuff in,
put in some oil in there, so maybe burnt umber, just try the straight burnt umber,
a bit of violet in there, yeah that didn't work very well,
ready to work in the actual paint, so I'm just going to look for that
colour, purple and green, work back into that, okay, try that again, violet burnt umber,
just a bit of brush, a bit of black, the darkest part, it's going to bring that chin back,
okay, that is the neck done,